<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Product on Defiant - Empowering Businesses with Innovative dApps, Full-Stack Web and Mobile Applications, and Fortified Cybersecurity Solutions</title>
    <link>https://www.thedefiant.in/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Product on Defiant - Empowering Businesses with Innovative dApps, Full-Stack Web and Mobile Applications, and Fortified Cybersecurity Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.thedefiant.in/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hornet</title>
      <link>https://www.thedefiant.in/services/hornet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.thedefiant.in/services/hornet/</guid>
      <description>Most of the payments for illegal activities on the Dark Web are done in cryptocurrencies like bitcoin, Ethereum, etc. because of the anonymity it provides. By regularly monitoring the transactions on the blockchain we can identify and take precautionary steps against the activity. But no such indigenous tool exists! We are here to build the software suite that can enable the military with that required intelligence.
&amp;ldquo;Hornet&amp;rdquo; is the wasp which can see in the dark and we the &amp;ldquo;Hornet&amp;rdquo; can see in the dark-web!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr Bin: The Smart Bin</title>
      <link>https://www.thedefiant.in/services/bin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.thedefiant.in/services/bin/</guid>
      <description>Smart waste management is an idea where we can control lots of problems like dirtiness, pollution and disease, by regularly cleaning up the waste bins only when required, not otherwise. The waste management has to be done instantly else it leads to irregular management which will have adverse effect on nature. The smart waste management is compatible mainly with the concept of smart cities.
Mr Bin: The Smart Bin The traditional way of manually monitoring the wastes is a time consuming and complex process which requires lots of human efforts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
